# 張簡婷尹

## Ting-Yin Chang Chien

+886 919 549 131 | tingyin.cc@gmail.com | tingyincc.github.io | github.com/tingyincc

#### PERSONAL STATEMENT

Software engineer with 2 years of experience in mechanical control programming and 2 year of experience in Deep learning. Longing to apply the learned to build practical tools for the user rather than diving deep into theory research. Fast learner with a can-do spirit and full of curiosity about new techniques.

#### **SKILLS**

Practice

Web Development (Django, Ruby on Rails), Computer Vision (OpenCV), Machine Learning (Tensorflow)

Coding

Python, C/C++, JavaScript, HTML/CSS, Ruby, C#, SQL

#### **EDUCATION**

#### BSc, Computer Science and Information Engineering (CSIE)

Sept. 2009 - June 2013

National Taiwan University (NTU)

Taipei, Taiwan

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Research Assistant Apr. 2018 – Present

Medical Computer-Aided Diagnosis System Lab, Dept. of CSIE, National Taiwan University

Taipei, Taiwan

- Conduct research on tumor-related images (breast tumor, lymph node, lung nodule images, etc.) detection and classification using machine learning/deep learning methods
- Reduced 87% of false positives (from 29.35 to 3.8) at 98% sensitivity (AUC = 0.961) and reduced 90% of execution time (from 11 sec. to 1 sec.) in tumor detection using the modified object detection system YOLO
- Design experiments, visualize test statistics, sort data, and help edit theses and publications
- Cooperate with postdoctoral researchers, students, physicians, and industrial companies

Software Engineer Jan. 2014 – Mar. 2016

Brogent Technologies Inc.

Kaohsiung, Taiwan

- Developed the central control system of two 4-D, somatosensory, 100-seat rides in C/C++
- Designed a new UI and implemented it in C#, saving 50% of UI implementation time for other control system developers
- Implemented an SQL database to record the 1 GB of daily machine activity data
- Led a team of four software engineers in two full-year projects: Yumble 4-D Theatre (Roermond, Netherlands) and Wildlands Adventure Zoo Emmen 4-D Theatre: Arctic 1 (Emmen, Netherlands)
- Collaborated with mechanical and electrical engineers to design the ride show cycle
- Installed facilities, coordinated with subcontractors on-site, and provided customer support

### PERSONAL PROJECTS

Lottery Dec. 2018 – Jan 2019

- Self-directed project. Built a website for playing the lottery using Django framework
- Implemented the backend with SQL database to let users import and modify awards and name lists
- Implemented the frontend and adjusted interfaces as per the customer's requirements in JavaScript and HTML/CSS

NTU COOL May 2018 – Jan. 2019

- Built the frontend of the e-Learning platform NTU COOL in JavaScript and HTML/CSS within Ruby on Rails framework; the platform lets NTU faculty members and students interact outside of courses
- Designed UI, UX, and marketing materials